https://newday.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Discover Grants, Scholarships, Aid Programs, Awards & More. Updated every Hour.
ADD YOUR LISTING
Privacy Policy.
We value your Privacy.
Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. And do not hesitate to get in touch with us in case you have any questions.
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.NewDay.org.PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including PayPal, bank account details, email address, and phone number).  We refer to this information as “Order Information”.When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Listing or Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISINGAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work .You can opt out of targeted advertising by:INCLUDE OPT-OUT LINKS FROM WHICHEVER SERVICES BEING USED.COMMON LINKS INCLUDE:FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/ .DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@newday.org or by mail using the details provided below:NewDay.orgKabul, AfghanistanEmail: privacy@NewDay.orgLast updated on: April 2019
NewDay.org is a community dedicated to Youth Employment and Youth Entrepreneurship. We inspire bold people with high aspirations to make an impact in their lives and communities.
funding types
Awards & Competitions
Conferences
Fellowships
Grants
Scholarships
ALL
categories
Rural Dev.
Arts & Culture
Democracy
Startups
Women
ALL
countries
Afghanistan
Bangladesh
Login with Facebook
personDon't have an account?
lockForgot password?
person
Create an account
Anti-spam
Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
Sign Up
Or connect with
Sign in with Google
Login with Facebook
Already Registered?
Cart
NewDay uses cookies to give you the best user experience. If you continue to use our services, we will assume that you agree to the use of such cookies. Find out more about cookies and how you can refuse them in our Privacy Policy.
GOT IT
